Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
7656
Les K. Wright
36.4 cubic feet and 4 volumes of scrapbooks
Newsletters, flyers, journals, personal memorabilia and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Documentation of a gay subculture revolving around burly, hairy men, or "bears." Includes newsletters, flyers, and correspondence from bear clubs, printouts from related electronic discussion lists, and material related to the writing and publication of THE BEAR BOOK, which Wright edited. Also, Wright's journals, personal memorabilia, and correspondence, including extensive correspondence with friend Billie Aul.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Documentation of a gay subculture revolving around burly, hairy men, or "bears." Includes newsletters, flyers, correspondence, and ephemera from bear clubs, printouts from related electronic discussion lists, and material related to the writing and publication of THE BEAR BOOK, which Wright edited. In addition, materials relating to the founding and running of the Nashoba Institute, a non-profit think tank focused on non-hegemonic masculinities.
Also, Wright's journals, personal memorabilia, and correspondence, including extensive correspondence with friend Billie Aul. Also included is much of Wright's academic work, notably his dissertation and tenure manuscripts, class syllabi, and other published and unpublished writings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wright, Les K.; Aul, Billie.
Titles:
Bear book.
Subjects:
Gays--Identity.; Gay men--Attitudes.; Gender identity.; Group identity.; Masculinity.; Body image.; Bears (Gay culture)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Journals and Personal Memorabilia
Boxes 2-3, 15-16, 37-49
This series contains documents from Wright's childhood through the time of the first donation in 2000. A school records book contains yearly photos of him and information about his teachers and classes from elementary through high school. There are additional mementos from high school, his senior year of high school spent in Germany, his years at the State University of New York at Albany, and his graduate work in comparative literature at the University of California- Berkeley, followed by files on his student loan payments. A draft of his dissertation, "The Chiasmic War: AIDS, Writing, and Gay Community in the US" is found here, as well as his dossier submitted for tenure review at Mount Ida College. The series includes his personal journals from 1970 to 1989, medical files from 1958 to 1995, files about receiving government assistance (welfare and Supplemental Security Income), mementos from places he lived and visited, and some family genealogy.
This series also contains a brown vinyl scrapbook in which he kept newspaper clipping and keepsakes from his youth through adulthood, 1966-1984. The scrapbook shows his early academic successes, Rotary award, and high school achievements and his later political affiliations and involvements. For instance, his membership cards for the American Civil Liberties Union and the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force are included. This scrapbook posed a preservation challenge due to its adhesives and plastics. To preserve a record of the way everything was originally laid out, we photocopied the contents onto acid-free paper. This copy is available in Box 2, folder 32. We removed items that were intact enough and not fused to the pages and are storing them in separate acid-free envelopes.
Series II. Publications and Academic Work
Boxes 3-4, 17-21, 26, 31, 36, 50-52
Publications contains Wright's files from his various writing projects on German literature, German gay history, US gay politics, gay literature, and the bear gay subculture. Included are numerous articles, his dissertation prospectus, and comments by Jim Jones and Billie Aul on the dissertation drafts. As part of his dissertation research, he also collected some files on gay communities in the Netherlands and other European countries. There are manuscripts from The Bear Book I and II, reviews, and correspondence with contributors. Additionally, there are research notes on the history of the Castro as a gay ghetto, utopia, and neighborhood, along with notes/correspondence regarding research into the lives of long-term HIV/AIDS survivors for the "Surviving Soul Murder" project (book?). Non-bear related conference materials where Wright led workshops are also included. There are also a large number of movie and book reviews written by Wright.
Subseries:
Dissertation Materials
Castro History Project
Surviving Soul Murder
Conferences/Workshops
Reviews
Published and Unpublished Articles
Academic Courses
Tenure Manuscript
Series III. Correspondence
Boxes 4-8, 21, 23-26, 36, 53
This series spans from 1968-2000 and is arranged alphabetically within the groups in which the material was received. Correspondents are many and include the Committee on Lesbian and Gay History, the Gay and Lesbian Historical Society of Northern California (GLHSNC), and a file of "Letters to Editors". The series also includes files of Wright's letters to Billie Aul and Ken Ratcliffe.
Series IV. Bear History Project
Boxes 3-4, 9-14, 21-22, 28-35, 54, 56-61
Newsletters and files on Bear clubs around the world (US, UK, Canada, Denmark, Germany, Australia, New Zealand, Finland, Switzerland), their events and publications, and printouts of an electronic mailing list for Bears from 1993 to 2000. There are also 2 scrapbooks compiled by Wright on the Monty Bear group in Fitchburg, MA, including photographs of events, flyers advertising events, and other miscellany. Also here are issues 1 to 17 of Bearskin Bend Lodge and issues 1 to 8 of the Bear History Project Newsletter.
Series V. Nashoba Institute
Boxes 22, 27, 55
Les Wright founded the Nashoba Institute, a non-profit think tank focused on non-hegemonic masculinities. Board documents and correspondence reflect the activities and ideas of the Institute.
Series VI. Audiovisual and Computer Media
Boxes 14, 31,
This series contains interviews and programs on Bear themes on audio and video cassettes and computer disks with Wright's writing, correspondence, mailing lists and other files
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Journals and Personal Memorabilia
  - School Records book containing information about elementary and high school, including school pictures, 1959-1971 (Box 15)
  - Scrap book containing newspaper clippings, various membership cards, photos (copy of contents in box 2, folder 32), 1966-1984 (Box 16)
  - Resume (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Journals, 1970-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2-14)
  - Medical, 1958-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - High School (things he saved), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Muelheim-Ruhr, Germany (Sr. Year Abroad), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Albany, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Beta Phi Sigma, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wurzburg, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Tubingen, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - San Francisco, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Programs from Conferences in which LKW participated, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Exams- MA and Ph.D., 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Articles, Brochures, Misc., 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27-28)
  - Welfare, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - SSI (Supplemental Security Income), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - LKW's dissertation draft "The Chiasmic War: AIDS, Writing, and Gay Community in the U.S.", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Photocopy of Scrap Book (along side of box), 1966-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Graduation Photo- Entire Class of 1971- Homer Central High School (on top of box), 1971 (Box 2)
  - Ph.D. Graduation Cards, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ASIF- Adult Survivors of Incest Foundation, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - SAA Social Security Administration, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Boston, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Student Loans- NY, CA, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Barb Macy, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Genealogy, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fitchburg, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Journals, 2007-2010 (Box 37)
  - Dream Book I (Box 38)
  - Disability and vocational Rehab, 2006-2009 (Box 38, Folder 1-2-3)
  - Les And Dale Robert Wehrie Civil Union, 2002; V-1 (Box 38)
  - Leslie Wright and Dale Wehrle - Civil Union in VT, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Photo Albums, 1974-Jan '79 (Box 39)
  - Photo Albums, Jan '79-Jan '89 (Box 40)
  - Photo Albums, June '89-Dec '93 (Box 41)
  - Photo Albums, Jan '94-Oct '96 (Box 42)
  - Photo Albums, 1997-Dec '99 (Box 43)
  - Photo Albums, 2000 (Box 44)
  - Photo Albums, 2000-2002 (Box 45, Folder 1-24)
  - Photo Albums, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 1-22)
  - Photo Albums, 2004-2006 (Box 47, Folder 1-20)
  - Christmas Cards and Brochures, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - LA Directories and Maps, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Mount Ida College - Faculty Bullying and Mobbing, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Cards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Loose Photos, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Postcards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Cinema Tickets and Visiting Card, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Cards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Loose Postcards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Loose Postcards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Loose Postcards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Cross-Country Trip, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Vacation Photos, 2003-2004; CD-713-725 (Box 48)
  - Photo Albums, 2005-2008 (Box 49)
  - Journal, February 2, 2010 - April 1, 2010 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Journal, April 1, 2010 - May 13, 2010 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Photo Albums, 1977-2009 (Box 72)
  - Nude and Erotica Photo Albums, n.d. (Box 72)
  - Bear Icons Photo Albums, 2008-2009 (Box 72)
  - Landscape Photo Albums, n.d. (Box 72)
  - Photo Albums, including holiday cards and postcards, circa 2008 (Box 73)
  - Photo Scrapbook, March 2008 - October 2008 (Volume 1)
  - Photo Scrapbook, October 2008 - December 2008 (Volume 2)
  - Photo Scrapbook, January 2009 - May 2009 (Volume 3)
  - Photo Scrapbook, June 2009 - January 2010 (Volume 4)
  - Acrylic on canvas, portrait of Les Wright and Dale Robert Wehrle (24"x24"), 2002 (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Series II. Publications and Academic Work
  - Dissertation Materials
    - Prospectus, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Dissertation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 79-81)
    - Dissertation with comments by Jim Jones, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Dissertation Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Early Draft of Dissertation with comments by Billie Aul, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Dissertation with comments by Billie Aul, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 85-87)
    - "Gay Genocide as Literary Trope: A Cautionary Reading of Cautionary Tales", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Chapter 0: Introduction, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 0: Introduction materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 1 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
    - Chapter 2: Canonicity, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 2 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Chapter 3: Urban Gay Male, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Chapter 3 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Chapter 4: The Castro, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Chapter 4 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Chapter 5: Wizard of Oz, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Chapter 5 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Chapter 6: Gay Genocide, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Chapter 6 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Chapter 7, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Chapter 7 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
    - Chapter 8, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Chapter 8 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Chapter 9, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Chapter 9 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Chapter 10, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Chapter 10 materials, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Bibliographies, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Graphics, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Dissertation publishing, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Dagestan, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Deutsche AIDS-Hilfe (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Germany (Box 17, Folder 31-32)
    - Germany: AIDS/Gay Bibliography (Box 17, Folder 33-34)
    - Gundlach Bundschu Winery (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - International Scientific Conference on Gay and Lesbian Studies, Amsterdam: "Current Issues" booklet, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Italy, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Netherlands (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - RFSC and Sweden, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 39-40)
    - Russia (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Summers, Gay and Lesbian Literature (mainly Germany, Australia), 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Sweden (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
    - Venema, Adriaan: "Homoseksualiteit in de Nederlandse literatuur", 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 2: Germany, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 2: Materials (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Vol. 3: Dutch Gay Pillar (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Castro History Project
    - AIDS Impact (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - AIDS (?), 1990, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Alamo Square Press, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bars (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bay Area Reporter Obituaries, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Castro Institutions (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - The Castro Theater, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Community, Ghetto, Migration, and Coming Out, 1996,1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Cops, Safety, Violence, Gay-Bashing, Homophobia, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Mount Ida College, and misc. materials, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Gay/Dyke Parades, 1986,1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - GLHS/NC (Gay and Lesbian Historical Society of Northern California) History/Historians, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - GLHS/NC Holdings (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - GLHS/NC "Castro Street" Subject File, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Graphics (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - "A Historical Directory of Lesbian and Gay Establishments in the San Francisco Bay Area" (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - The Imagined, Utopian, Literary Locus, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Necropolis, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Gay History Outline (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Periodicals of San Francisco (SF): Newspapers (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Russian River, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - SF AIDS P.H. (?) Response, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - SF Queer Materials, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Misc. research materials (Box 18, Folder 33-37)
    - Misc. research materials (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
    - Barragan, Chuck, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Botkin, Michael, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Diamon, N.A., 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Gerrits, Burt, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Nicoletta, Danny, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - O'Connell, Dan (Beacon Press), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Surviving Soul Murder
    - Sabbatical 2001-2002, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - "Surviving Soul Murder" proposal, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Materials on Long Term AIDS Survivors, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 21-61)
      Includes correspondence, materials from internet message boards, interview release forms, etc. Arranged alphabetically by last name or pseudonym.
    - "After the Dying" by Benjamin Klein, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - AIDS, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - AIDS as Existentialist Problem, 1986-1987,1997 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Articles on AIDS, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Check List Form (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - "Dead" or Dead Contacts, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - e-mail correspondence, including long-term survivor e-group, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Harvard Student Global AIDS Coalition Speech, August 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - CD of Les Wright Kick-off speech, Harvard U. Science Center, for AIDS Awareness Week 2002, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "HIV and Self Growth" by Steve Heinzen, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Interview Guidelines (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Kelly", 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mangiapane- "Memories of Mario" (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Misc. materials, including notes, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 8-11)
    - Original Release Forms, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Misc. materials, in English and German, 1987,1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Poz social groups around the country, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Poz Gentleman's Quality Circle Yahoo e-group, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "pozsurvivor" Yahoo e-group, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - pozsurvivors e-group correspondence, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Release Forms (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - "The Trouble with Nevirapine" by Anthony Brink, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Toth, Rober (poz e-group), 2002 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Conferences/Workshops
    - AMSA (American Men's Studies Association) Conference, April 2004 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - GMHS (Gay Men's Health Summit) LTS Panel/Workshop, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - IGLMA (International Gay and Lesbian Medical Association?) "Trauma Theory and Alcoholism" rewrite draft, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Lavender Languages Conference, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Lavender Languages Conference: Homophobic Speech Acts, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Maine Gay Men's Health Conference, May 1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - NEATE (New England Association of Teachers of English): AIDS in the Humanities, English Classroom, October 1994 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - OutWrite: Apocalyptic Narratives, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Queer Masculinities Conference, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 32-33)
    - Sexuality & Spirituality Talk/Presentation, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Sexuality & Spirituality Master Hand-outs, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Gay Men's Spirituality Discussion Group, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - "True Colors" Workshop, March 2004 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Outwrite, 1993-1995 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Conferences and workshops (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Gay Men Health's Summit, 2001-2003 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Reviews
    - And the Band Played On, Randy Shilts, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Third Sex by J. Jones and Gestalt des Schoenen by Gerhard Haerle, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Bord de Mer, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Cody Adams, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Gauguin Tahiti, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Golden Gate Bridge by PBS, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Mapping Murder, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Me and Mrs. Jones, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Mount Airy, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Orwell Rolls in his Grave, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Passion of the Christ, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Six Feet Under Season 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Take Me, by the BBC, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - A Tickle in the Heart, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Wire in the Blood Season 2 (BBC America), 2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Journal of Homosexuality Review: "Gay, Observant, and Torn", 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - An Unfinished life, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - On a clear day, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - End of August at Hotel Ozone, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Friends with money, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Sir!No Sir!, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Lonesome Jim, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Brick, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - The Devil and Daniel Johnston, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Same sex America, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Don't come knocking, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Cafe Lumiere, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Annapolis, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - The world fastest Indian, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Curious George, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Firewall, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - C.S.A:The Confederate States of America, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Go for Zucker, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - O.K, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Barefoot (Barfus), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - The new world, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - End of the spear, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - The three burial of Melquiades Estrada, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Looking for comedy in the muslim world, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Fateless, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - The shaggy dog, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Citizen dog, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Grain in ear, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - The Zodiac, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Evil, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Water, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Kiev, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Match Point, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - The matador, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Sophie Scholl:The final days, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Following Sean, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - The white countess, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Netto, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - harry Potter and the globes of fire, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - A touch of spice, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Rent, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Tom Brown's School Days, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - 39 Pounds of love, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - One...The movie, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Flightplan, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - The thing about my folks, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Memoires of a Geisha, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - The Chronicles of Narnia, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - The producers, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - Mr. Harvey lights a candle, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - Pulse, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - Transamerica, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - The family Stone, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - The ringer, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - Waging a living, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - The libertine, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - Sons of Sparrows, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - Bear run, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - I wake up dreaming:The haunted world of B Film Noir, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - Watchmen, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 59-60)
    - Moscow, Belgium, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - A Jihad for love, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - The Bible tells me so, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - Trade, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Bears, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - Four minutes, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - The witnesses, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - Summer in Berlin, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Sound of the soul, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - La vie en Rose, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - The rape of Europa, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Pervert, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Man push cart, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 73)
    - The life of others, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - The astronaut farmer, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Lumber rings, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - The fisherman and his wife, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Volver, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Haven, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Jonestown:the life and death of the people temple, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 80)
    - Zen Noir, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 81)
    - Al Franken: God spoke, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 82)
    - Marie Antoinette, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 83)
    - Death of a president, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 84)
    - Stranger than fiction, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 85)
    - Old Joy, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 86)
    - Queens (Reinas), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 87)
    - My country, my country, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 88)
    - The quiet, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 89)
    - The fifth horseman is fear, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 90)
    - Half Nelson, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 91)
    - Factotum, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 92)
    - The house of sand, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 93)
    - Quinceanera, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 94)
    - Leonard Cohen, I'm your man, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 95)
    - Army of shadows, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 96)
    - Superman returns, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 97)
    - Lemming, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 98)
    - Twelve and holding, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 99)
    - Cars, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 100)